{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255838019","data":{"timestamp":" 947255838019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_550_554-251-550"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 550"," userResponse":" 554"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255847420","data":{"timestamp":" 947255847420"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_550_554-251-550"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 550"," userResponse":" 550"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255861310","data":{"timestamp":" 947255861310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_636_513-636-381"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 636"," userResponse":" 381"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255870718","data":{"timestamp":" 947255870718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_636_513-636-381"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 636"," userResponse":" 636"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255890602","data":{"timestamp":" 947255890601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_365_372-365-422"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 365"," userResponse":" 372"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255900028","data":{"timestamp":" 947255900027"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_365_372-365-422"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 365"," userResponse":" 365"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255914251","data":{"timestamp":" 947255914251"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_715_320-715-437"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 715"," userResponse":" 715"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255926975","data":{"timestamp":" 947255926975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_538_296-538-315"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 538"," userResponse":" 538"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255937793","data":{"timestamp":" 947255937793"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_626_258-626-107"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 626"," userResponse":" 626"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255955842","data":{"timestamp":" 947255955842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_388_322-388-533"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 388"," userResponse":" 388"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255966718","data":{"timestamp":" 947255966718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_461_261-461-429"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 461"," userResponse":" 461"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255984017","data":{"timestamp":" 947255984016"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_594_594-211-375"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 594"," userResponse":" 594"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947255994972","data":{"timestamp":" 947255994971"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 324"," userResponse":" 285"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256005384","data":{"timestamp":" 947256005384"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 324"," userResponse":" 326"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256015125","data":{"timestamp":" 947256015125"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 324"," userResponse":" 324"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256024771","data":{"timestamp":" 947256024770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256031940","data":{"timestamp":" 947256031940"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256039366","data":{"timestamp":" 947256039365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256046009","data":{"timestamp":" 947256046009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:73..973.off100.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256097156","data":{"timestamp":" 947256097156"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:73..973.off100.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256144707","data":{"timestamp":" 947256144706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_173659"," gameId":" 478cfc1e-826f-4797-a327-bc376e49163e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}